## **AYAZ ZAFAR**

### TIPTON, UNITED KINGDOM

🔾 07465 206505 🏻 🔁 ayaziqbalzafar@gmail.com

(f) https://ayazzafar.com in https://linkedin.com/in/ayaz-zafar



## **About Me**

A highly motivated and hardworking individual, who has experience in IT & in Pharmacy Dispensing. I work exceptionally well in a team both as a leader and a follower as I believe that great companies are built on teamwork and cooperation.

# **Experience**

#### Locum | Jan 2023 - Present

Locum Pharmacy Dispenser

Receive and store medications coming into the pharmacy, maintain stock of prescription medications, keep records and maintain an inventory of drugs to facilitate the role of a Pharmacist.

#### I-Dispense | Jun 2022 - Mar 2023

Pharmacy Dispenser

Receive and store medications coming into the pharmacy, maintain stock of prescription medications, keep records and maintain an inventory of drugs to facilitate the role of a Pharmacist.

#### JD Sports | Nov 2021 - Jan 2022

Sales Assistant

Greeting Customers as they enter the store and as they leave, Keeping the store well maintained, Helping Customers by asking, them if they need any help.

#### Appstack | Dec 2020 - Apr 2021

Web Developer

- · Designing Websites and Apps
- · Maintain and Update Websites
- · Experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and other relevant Web Design Coding Language

## Education

#### **Dudley College of Technology | Sep 2022 - Present**

Systems Support for IT Technicians Diploma - Level 3

- · Customer Support Provision · Networking Principles
- · Maintain Equipment & Systems · Install & Configure Networks
- Install & Configure Software
  Acquisition & Delivery ICT Support & System
- · Repair Centre Procedures

#### Dudley College of Technology | Sep 2021 - Jun 2022

Systems Support for IT Technicians Diploma - Level 2

- · Customer Support Provision · Networking Principles
- · Maintain Equipment & Systems · Install & Configure Networks
- · Software Installation · Testing Equipment · Systems and Data Security
- · Repair Centre Procedures · Visual Basic

### Leasowes High School | Sep 2016 - Jun 2021

GCSE, Computer Science

#### School of Coding | Nov 2020 - Feb 2021

Training, Web Developer

- Codina
- Designing Websites
- · Python, HTML, CSS & JavaScript

# **Qualifications**

Level 2 Diploma in ICT Systems and Principles for IT Professionals **Buttercups Level 2 Pharmacy Dispenser**